So now let's get
into the code-related tools in AWS.
So before pushing the application code to servers,
you need to store it somewhere.
And developers usually choose a code repository.
Usually that was going to be backed
using the Git technology, G-I-T.
And so a very famous public offering is called GitHub.
But AWS has a competing product.
That is going to be CodeCommit.
And so CodeCommit is a way for you
to store your code
within AWS in a version control repository.
So it's going to be for Git-based repository.
And why would you have that?
Well, once you have a Git-based repository,
it becomes incredibly easy for developers
to collaborate with each other on the code.
The code changes are going
to be automatically versioned and can be rolled back.
And so the benefit is that with CodeCommit,
you have a fully-managed code repository.
It's scalable and highly available,
but also it lives within your AWS accounts.
So it's private, secure,
and it's going to be integrated with all AWS services.
So I will see you in the next lecture.